unlocklink.com 2008-05-10

# Unlocklink.com - Store & Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We are committed to protecting your privacy.

This privacy statement discloses what information we gather about you when you visit our store and describes how we use that information. Our policy is to keep the personal information we receive from our Site completely confidential and used solely for internal purposes. We will not share your personal information with any other parties.

**Collection of your Personal Information:**

The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, e-mail, address, and phone number. We may collect certain information about your visit, such as type of browser you use; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our Site. This information is used to help improve the Site and administer the Site.

**Use of your Personal Information:**

The personal information collected on this Site will be used to provide the services you have requested.  
We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications. Additionally, we may send you information about other products and services.

## Store Policy

By placing an order on this site, the buyer must agree fully to the compliance of the following terms and conditions. Unlocklink.com reserves the right to take any legal action against the buyer if terms and policy is violated.

**Payments**

Unlocklink.com proudly uses Interac™ Email Money Transfer for all e-commerce transactions on our site, but we also accept Paypal or Cash.

  * If choosing **Paypal** an additional charge of 3.0% will be added in your total to cover the fees.
  * If choosing **Email Money Transfer (EMT)** all EMT are to be send to email: henwyc@gmail.com. If payment are not received within the 24 hours of purchase your order will be cancelled.
  * If choosing **Local Pick Up pay in Cash** please state the desirable location to meet up. (Richmond Hill , Markham or Mississauga) in the text box below, otherwise your order will be cancelled. Upon receiving your order our representative will contact you regarding the location, date and time.

**Prices**

Product prices on the site are subjected to be changed at any time based on the market trends and values. Unlocklink also holds the right to reject any orders that have been placed on an item that had a mis-typed or wrong pricing in our catalogue. It is also important to note that the prices listed on the site do not include additional costs like surcharges for certain payment types, shipping costs etc. Such additional costs will be reflected on your shopping cart once you will be ready to checkout.

**Shipping**

For information on how soon your order will be shipped out, please see the Availability field on the product detail page. As soon as your item is shipped, you will receive an email with the status update.   
Orders received after 5:00 PM Eastern Time (GMT - 5:00) will start processing on the next business day.   
Normal processing time for an order is taken within 24-48 hrs after a full compliance payment is received by Unlocklink.com. 

**Delivery Dates**

Delivery dates within Canada are approximations and are shipped to the best of our ability. Delivery dates outside of Canada are approximations that do not include possible delays due to customs and/or weather conditions

**Warranty**

All sales are final. There is no refund or exchange. All products come with 1 year manufacture’s warranty.   
For all pick up customers, it is their responsibility to check the phone themselves before leaving the pick up area. All sales are still subject to the 1 year manufacture’s warranty.   
Manufacture’s warranty does not include physical damage, water damage or software deficiencies. Customers are to contact manufactures themselves if their products are in need of repair. 

\---------------------------

**Questions:**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or concerns about the way we process your Personal Data, please contact us using the Contact Us form. 

We may occasionally modify this privacy statement. All such changes will be reflected on this web page.
